{
    "id": "36d16f3d219f4e6da137fc1d792ea510",
    "title": "Common Idioms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was not at all impressed when I told her that she looked old in that outfit. Me and my …………………… mouth!",
            "description": "Used to refer to a person who talks too much, especially about things that should be secret",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "bad",
                "foul"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c4e75c4834d49a6bdd506e28beacd1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I really want to help you, but my ………………………. are tied.",
            "description": "When your hands are tied, something prevents you from doing what you would normally have the power to do. ",
            "answers": [
                "legs",
                "hands",
                "fingers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a80e0127584c48e9aa75c7b191b5404d"
        },
        {
            "question": "My ……………………..  goes out to the families of the kids who died in the mishap.",
            "description": "When your heart goes out to someone, you feel great sympathy for them.",
            "answers": [
                "mind",
                "heart",
                "brain"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ead160b9fc314ae5b7306562b10c6202"
        },
        {
            "question": "She might come across as a snobbish woman, but I’m sure she has her ………………………… in the right place.",
            "description": "To have your heart in the right place is to have right intentions.",
            "answers": [
                "mind",
                "heart",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75edcd8e51044b6e9f7990ab6c69c872"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your ……………………….. isn’t in it. Otherwise, you wouldn’t make so many silly mistakes.",
            "description": "If your heart isn't in something you're doing, you don't really want to do it or you make numerous mistakes.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "mind",
                "heart"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "edbdf241a65b49ababe7d3982d2dece8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He started preparing for the exams months in advance and that sort of gave him a ……………………… start.",
            "description": "If you have a head start, you start doing something ahead of others.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "big",
                "clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e05b5f3d696742d8977a8e718d9fb7f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Almost all of us have a ……………………. in the closet.",
            "description": "To have a skeleton in the closet is to hide a shocking secret about yourself.",
            "answers": [
                "skeleton",
                "secret",
                "skull"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65da826037fe4f9483f8fc7997da25e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of our politicians are ………………………… skinned.",
            "description": "If you have a thick skin you don’t get upset when people criticize you.",
            "answers": [
                "thick",
                "thin",
                "light",
                "dark"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f19f2578d10749d886fb42b5bb6c338c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He escaped from the burning building by the ……………………… of his teeth.",
            "description": "If you do something by the skin of your teeth, you only just manage to do it. ",
            "answers": [
                "tip",
                "skin",
                "root"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54cef8bab841441e9d85558022103efc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did really well on the TOEFL test after he got his ……………………….. into learning English.",
            "description": " To get your teeth into something is to get completely involved in it.",
            "answers": [
                "nails",
                "teeth",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da898f59b33c4a9d923cd538da555e4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You may not have liked what I said, but that doesn’t mean that you’ve to jump down my ………………………...",
            "description": "To jump down someone’s throat is to react angrily to something that they say or do.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "neck",
                "throat"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be28c6277f734194980af48b6f4d1c96"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at her garden. Beautiful, isn’t it? She really has a",
            "description": "If you have a green thumb, you are very good at gardening.",
            "answers": [
                "pink",
                "red",
                "green"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05b87b1f229249a687a260ec4fd12e29"
        }
    ]
}